{
    "subject": "Mongkut",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Pannarai",
    "human_readable": "Mongkut is married to Pannarai.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9146654605865479,
            "question": "To whom is Mongkut married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9120379686355591,
            "question": "Is Mongkut married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8763856887817383,
            "question": "Who is married to Pannarai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8672603964805603,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the relationship between Mongkut and Pannarai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8537349700927734,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Mongkut and Pannarai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8469294905662537,
            "question": "Name one person married to Pannarai."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8053514361381531,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Mongkut and Pannarai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7671669721603394,
            "question": "What is the name of the person married to Pannarai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6102457642555237,
            "question": "Who is Mongkut?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09234502166509628,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this relationship?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mongkut is married to Pannarai.",
            "html": "yago_23361_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Mongkut?",
            "html": "yago_23361_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the person married to Pannarai?",
            "html": "yago_23361_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between Mongkut and Pannarai?",
            "html": "yago_23361_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23361_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}\n\nThe documents mention that Mom Chao Chae (Pannarai) and her sister Mom Chao Rampoei Siriwongse became the consorts of King Mongkut in 1851. This suggests a marital relationship between Pannarai and Mongkut, making the statement correct according to the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Pannarai was a consort of King Mongkut, which supports the statement that Mongkut is married to Pannarai."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}